homeimpovement.com 2004-06-05

# HomeMortgageRates.com

**

HOMEMORTGAGERATES.COM PRIVACY POLICY

**

HomeMortgageRates.com ("HomeMortgageRates") is owned by LoanCalculator.com, and we respect your right to privacy and we understand that visitors to www.HomeMortgageRates.com need to be in control of their personal information. We also want to present information on www.HomeMortgageRates.com that is tailored to the needs of our visitors. For this reason, we may ask you to register or to provide personal information when you sign up for free loan advice, visit certain areas of www.HomeMortgageRates.com, download free software, enter a contest, order products, or subscribe to a newsletter. If you choose not to register you will not have access to areas that require personal identification. 

We will use the personal information you share with us to:

> Help us tailor the content, services, goods, and advertising that we provide on www.HomeMortgageRates.com(and related sites) to your current and future needs.   
>  Alert you via e-mail to new features, special offers, updated information, and new services. 

**

How HomeMortgageRates will protect your personal information

**

HomeMortgageRates will protect the personal information that you share with us as described below: 

We will not share your personal information with third parties (aside from entities that perform services for us, such as fulfilling orders, that either are bound to comply with our privacy policy or have privacy policies that protect your information) without your permission, as explained in the "opt-out" section below. 

Your personal information is password-protected, and you should take appropriate measures to protect the secrecy of your password. If you use a computer in a public place or share a computer with others, remember to sign out and close your browser window when you finish a session with www.HomeMortgageRates.com in order to prevent others from accessing your personal information.

HomeMortgageRates may disclose information you provide if required to do so by law or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is necessary to (1) comply with the law or with legal process served on www.shockwave.com; (2) protect and defend the rights or property of HomeMortgageRates; or (3) act in an emergency to protect someone's safety.

If we gather demographic information from you (for example, your age, education level or household income), we will not share that information in a manner that identifies you as an individual with any other entity, unless we let you know that at the time of collection. When we share demographic information with third parties, we will give them aggregate information only. HomeMortgageRates may carefully select third parties to send you information about their products or services unless you have "opted-out" as described below.

**

How to opt-out

**

If you do not want to receive information from HomeMortgageRates or third parties that we have selected, you may decline to receive it by contacting info@loancalculator.com or by postal mail at the address below:

LoanCalculator.com  
PO BOX 933

Fairport, NY 14450

ATTN: HomeMortgageRates Privacy  

**

What information we collect

**

When you register, www.HomeMortgageRates.com asks for your e-mail address, first name and last name, and we may ask you to provide personal information. If we plan to share that information with the sponsor(s) or with others, we will provide a statement to that effect.

**

Your IP Address

**

An Internet Protocol (IP) address is unique string of numbers that is assigned to your computer by your Internet Service Provider. Web servers automatically identify your computer by its IP address. We will use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, and to administer our Web site. Your IP address also may be used to gather broad demographic information. 

**

Cookies

**

A "cookie" is a small line of text that is stored with your Web browser for record-keeping purposes and to help us provide better service to you. Your browser has options to accept, reject, or provide you with notice when a cookie is sent. We use cookies to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site. We also use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests. 

**

DoubleClick Banner Advertisements

**

We use an outside ad company, DoubleClick, to serve ads on our site. In the process of serving ads, DoubleClick places a DoubleClick cookie in your browser's cookie file. By delivering ads on the www.HomeMortgageRates.com site, DoubleClick is able to record what ads a browser - identified by the unique cookie - has seen, and what www.HomeMortgageRates.com web site pages the browser was viewing when the ads were delivered. This web usage information is combined with other ad delivery information DoubleClick has (e.g., what type of operating system your computer uses). The information is used as part of the ad serving process for reporting and to target the ads you see online. Unlike the cookies HomeMortgageRates uses in other parts of our Web site, cookies received with banner ads are collected by DoubleClick and we do not have access to this information.

Additionally, some ads served by DoubleClick are generated by third party ad serving systems that also may place a cookie on your browser to provide web usage information to those third parties. To find out more about those specific third party ad serving systems, please click to their sites below:  

We recognize that not all users wish to receive ads targeted to their interests and we put the wishes of our users first. We want you to have the choice. If you want to learn more about DoubleClick's ad serving, privacy policies and the use of cookies, please visit the DoubleClick site at [www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy/privacy.htm](http://www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy/privacy.htm). 

If you would like to opt-out of DoubleClick's cookie now click here: [www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy/privacy.htm](http://www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy/privacy.htm).

For us at HomeMortgageRates, the most important thing is that you make the choice that is best for you.

****

**DARTmail Express**  
HomeMortgageRates has partnered with DoubleClick to make DARTmail Express, an Opt-In Email solution available to www.HomeMortgageRates.com users. Based on information your specify, DARTmail Express connects you with organizations that are able to provide relevant, timely information, offers and discounts to you via email. Participation in the DARTmail program is completely voluntary and is only available to users over the age of 18. 

If you would like to subscribe to DARTmail Express or review more detailed information about DARTmail Express, please [click here](http://www.shockwave.com/bin/shockwave/account/dartmail/form.jsp):

You may unsubscribe to DARTmail Express at any time by clicking on the link below.  

To find out more about DoubleClick's DARTmail Express service, please visit the DoubleClick site at: [http://www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy/privacy.htm](http://www.doubleclick.net/privacy_policy/privacy.htm) **

Links to other sites

** The www.HomeMortgageRates.com site contains links to other sites. HomeMortgageRates is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites. **

Security measures

** HomeMortgageRates has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. These include a firewall to prevent unauthorized access to our systems and maintenance of registration information in a separate database. Although we will exercise reasonable care in providing secure transmission of information between your computer and our servers, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information transmitted to us over the Internet. **  
**

**

HomeMortgageRates.com's policy for data from children

**

HomeMortgageRates does not collect data from individuals that identify themselves as children under the age of 13 or sell products for purchase by children. The www.HomeMortgageRates.com site is not intended for use by children under the age of 13.  
If HomeMortgageRates becomes aware that it has received information from a child under the age of 13, we will respond to the inquiry, if appropriate, and will delete all personally identifiable information (including email address) concerning that child from our records. That information will not be used for any other purposes, nor will it be disclosed to any other parties.

If a parent believes that his or her child has submitted personal information to shockwave.com, they may contact us at info@HomeMortgageRates.com or by postal mail. 

HomeMortgageRates will promptly delete the information upon learning that it relates to a child. As noted above, HomeMortgageRates will not knowingly collect any information from a child.

HomeMortgageRates believes that parents should supervise their children's online activities and consider using parental control tools available from online services and software manufacturers that help provide a kid-friendly online environment. These tools can also prevent children from otherwise disclosing online their name, address, and other personal information without parental permission. 

**

How to update your Profile or contact HomeMortgageRates

**

You can help HomeMortgageRates maintain the accuracy of your profile by notifying us when you change your address, title, phone number, or e-mail address. If at any time you wish to update your information or stop receiving communication from HomeMortgageRates, our partners, or selected third parties, you may contact us at info@loancalculator.com or by postal mail. 

Please include your old and new contact information so that we can make the appropriate corrections. 

**

Changes to Our Policy

**

HomeMortgageRates will notify you of changes to its user privacy and information usage practices by posting the changes on this page. Please check the revision date at the bottom of this Privacy Policy to determine if the policy has been modified since you last reviewed it.

**

HomeMortgageRates would like to receive your comments and questions about this policy 

**

Please address comments or questions regarding HomeMortgageRates's privacy practices to us at one of the addresses listed above. **Conditions of Use**  
Your use of www.HomeMortgageRates.com, including any dispute concerning privacy, is subject to this Policy. **By using the www.HomeMortgageRates.com site, you are accepting the practices set out in our Privacy Policy.**

 ****

1/1/00
